Found out
Treasures are always lost
Pleasures and rage combined
I’m watchin’ you
Be careful with your moves
Tonight
I think the time is right
I think the blood has dried
It cries for more
So what are we waiting for?
Wires and chains
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
Starting to fade
Feels like a game
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
You have to play
Lights out
Is this who you really are
Can’t look into your eyes
Your twisted mind
It’s dark, so dark
We end it now
It ends right here, right now
Please tell me you brought the iron
Let’s light up the sky
And fade into the night
Wires and chains
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
Starting to fade
Feels like a game
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
You have to play
The days when it was good are gone
I’m tryna’ see what it was for, but I’ll never know
And though it’s dead I hear the call
Ooh
Wires and chains
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
Starting to fade
Feels like a game
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
You can't escape
Wires and chains
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
Starting to fade
Feels like a game
[Backing] I’m just tired of looking the other way
You can't escape
I found out
Treasures are always lost
Pleasures are long forgotten
Who are you now